Anupam Poudel

I am a self-motivated and self-dedicated person with a Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science and Information Technology. I am a fast learner with strong English communication and documentation skills. I have a significant passion for teamwork and collaboration. Worked more than 4 months as a Frontend Developer and more than 4 months as a Fullstack developer. I also have been involved in several Freelancing Fullstack Projects as well. I have experience in working with the latest Javascript Technologies.

Gaurighat
Kathmandu, Nepal
(977) 9860679848
anupampoudel78@gmail.com
linkedIn.com/in/anupampoud

Github: AnupamPoudel1

EXPERIENCE

Info Shapers PVT. LTD, Kathmandu — Full Stack Developer

February 2024 - June 2024

I was involved with Info Shapers as a Jr Full Stack Developer where I worked with technologies such as JavaScript , React JS, Express JS, Node JS, MongoDB, mySQL, Tailwind CSS, ShadCN UI and many more.

RGB I.T Solutions, Kathmandu — Frontend Developer

September 2023 - December 2023

I was involved with RGB IT solutions as a Jr Front End Developer. I got experience working with programming languages like React JS, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS, API integration and many more.

PROJECTS

Skill Spot Australia — *Online blog and news website*

Skill Spot Australia is an online blog and news website where users can visit and check different blogs and news related to organization. It also includes a client portal for clients to get their certificates.

WCKF — Online blog website for a karate organization

A karate website for World Christian Karate Federation where users can visit the website and check services and options provided by the organization. The user can also view different associated members and visit different blogs and news related to the organization.

Sr Aqua And Pet House — *online e-commerce website* sraquaandpethouse.com

Website for a Fish Shop. This website offers users to go to the website, visit and explore different kinds of products and services offered by the shop. It also contains Admin login through which an admin can change existing products and services or even add new products and services to the website.

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Tailwind CSS

React JS

Axios

Typescript

Node Js

Express Js

MongoDB

Mongoose

mySQL

LANGUAGES

English

Nepali

Chessmate — Online chess bot website

Chess mate is my final year project for completion of Bachelors of Science in Computer Science and Information Technology. This was made using JavaScript and Express Js where a user can register and login in-order to play against a chess bot of varying strength.

EDUCATION

Ambition Academy, Baneshowr — B.Sc. CSIT

2019 - Current

Currently waiting for my final semester results.

Riviera International Academy, Chabhil — SLC

2017 - 2019

Hillary High School, Gaurighat — SEE

2017 - 2019

Certifications

Web Development, Aptech Academy, Lalitpur

HTML, SoloLearn

CSS, SoloLearn